[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Can it take him all the way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "As president of the United States, I'll have your back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBZ", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "What does he say about ads like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Mitt Romney's ugly attacks are going to backfire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Because a lot rests on that, I would imagine, in terms of where the investigation goes, in terms of which doctor she was seeing, which prescriptions, what drugs she was actually taking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "WDT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "That the drugs that they found in her hotel room should not be mixed with alcohol, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "Is it unique to Los Angeles and the way that that is allowed to happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "TEINBERG: I don't think it's unique to Los Angeles.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Would it be negligent for a doctor to prescribe Whitney Houston with the kind of prescription drugs she had if they knew her to be an addict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, it depends on a lot of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard that Whitney Houston had died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "You know, my reaction was I took to my Twitter account and I said, what's scummy about the music industry is that everybody loves you when you're dead.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "DT", "WP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "At what point do we lose the courage and we started letting the other people run our lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I mean what's been a common theme throughout the week from the guests I've had is those who knew Whitney Houston saying she was very strong-willed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "What would you say to that argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I, too, am very strong-willed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Is it pills?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "It has been, at times --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "All?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "OUSTON: At times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "If you had to name the devil, for you, the biggest devil among them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "That would be me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "How easy has it been over the years for you to get pretty much any drug you like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "You know, I'm in a unique situation there where I actually never had a rock doc as they call them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "How do these rock docs go about their business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "You know I don't really understand how it works.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "And Piers, can I ask you a question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "If I went to your house for dinner and you know I'm a recovering alcoholic, and I ask for a glass of wine with dinner, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, this to me comes to the absolute crux of this, because you know, it's not like we are best friends or I know you that well, but I do know that you are a recovering addict.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "How can we hold them accountable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I think that is the key question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Why don't you think she wanted to get sober?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Well, it's a program of action sobriety, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What's your reaction to that as a former addict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Well, I mean, it's twofold.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "What was -- how did you find her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Very engaging.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "All this, if you were genuinely concerned about her, wouldn't you do something to stop this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Or in the end, did it have to come from within?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Well, both of those.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Karen"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "You must be enjoying yourself, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "It was that interview with Karen and the kids that launched this, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "How do you explain that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Well, the establishment has always been for Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Do you think that Newt Gingrich should pull out now, as some people are suggesting today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Oh, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["three million dollars"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", ":", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "And how much money have you earned in those four years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Cumulatively, just off the top of my head, it's probably a little -- over three million dollars in those four years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "So pretty successful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "No, I feel -- look, I feel very blessed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "How do you think the way the public will react to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, all my income is earned income.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "How would you summarize them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Well, I have been very blessed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Catholic Church"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Is that what your position on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Well, that's the Catholic Church's position, period, that it's wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Well, I mean, you know, you see this problem on the -- on the screen, where folks who are very famous -- as you know, in your own country, you go back into the examples of the aristocracy and the impact on the rest of society throughout the history of Britain, and vice versa, when -- when the aristocracy changed their behavior.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "There should be some more controlled regulation of this, to stop this sort of accepted practice over there, where you can almost go to 20 doctors if you want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "EX", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Well, it shouldn't be accepted practice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Where did that voice come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "So the whole family sings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "I know that she was something special to you, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "ESTMAN: She has a rich voice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "How did you feel when you heard that she had died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I was heart broken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Were you watching the Grammys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I actually was, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "And when you saw yourself coming up on a bus singing like Adele, what did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I mean, it appeared unexpectedly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Adele"]}}]